<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Root of Pi</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/</link><description>Recent content on Root of Pi</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rootofpi.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Personal Profile API built with Go Lang</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/projects/golang-api/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rootofpi.co.uk/projects/golang-api/</guid><description>An experimental and contrived preview of Golang. A very simple event driven API to fetch information about the Author, Michael Pearce. See if at api.michaelpearce.info
Source Code | Try it!</description></item><item><title>Turn the Ship Around!</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/turntheshiparound/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/turntheshiparound/</guid><description>L. David Marquet Hard to relate to at first, but overlal some really good insights into empowering people and turning followers into leaders. I really liked how each chapter ends with a section on questions to consider following the topic or theme of the chapter. There is definitely a lot of things that a lot of people can learn from this book!
Also checkout videos of talk David has presented, and there a some really good animation/voice over summaries of the book too.</description></item><item><title>Shoe Dog</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/shoe-dog/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/shoe-dog/</guid><description>Phil Knight A memoir by the creator of Nike.
Quite a complelling recollection of where it all began for Nike - trials and tribulations included.
True story, while the weather was good and I was sat outside reading the book in various places around the city three different people stopped to say they&amp;rsquo;d read the book and really enjoyed it!
Official Publisher Page</description></item><item><title>Funny you should ask...</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/funnyyoushouldask/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/funnyyoushouldask/</guid><description>Your questions answered by the QI elves A good mix of quirky, interesting and funny facts and theories!
Inspired by The Why Workshop on BBC Radio 2</description></item><item><title>Kafka On The Shore</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/kafkaontheshore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/kafkaontheshore/</guid><description>Haruki Murakami A trippy one, which I guess you could in part classify as sci-fi. There were uncomfortable parts, but something hypnotic about the time travel, eery coincidences, and profecies that saved it for me. Interestingly alternating chapters read through two distinct but later (as the book progresses) interrelated plots.
Why should you read “Kafka on the Shore”? - Iseult Gillespie</description></item><item><title>Noise Damage, My life as a rock and roll underdog</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/noisedamage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/noisedamage/</guid><description>James Kennedy Best book I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up in a while! Insightful and enlightening, adding some humour to the dark realities of the music scene. Easy to read, hard to put down.
Buy the book</description></item><item><title>Slaughterhouse Five, or The Children's Crusade</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/slaughterhouse5/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/slaughterhouse5/</guid><description>Kurt Vonnegut Biography of KV</description></item><item><title>IaC, Tools of the Trade</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/projects/toolsofthetrade/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rootofpi.co.uk/projects/toolsofthetrade/</guid><description>Infrastructure as Code: Tools of the trade. Presented in collaboration with Manhattan Partners this is an Introduction to Infrastructure as Code (scripted infrastructure), the pros/cons, examples, popular tools and frameworks.
Presentation | Watch the talks</description></item><item><title>The Unfettered Mind</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/unfetteredmind/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/unfetteredmind/</guid><description> Takuan Soho</description></item><item><title>Dark Matter</title><link>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/darkmatter/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://rootofpi.co.uk/books/darkmatter/</guid><description>Blake Crouch The first fiction book I’ve ready in a while, and a grippingly surreal one at that. Moving through a multiverse of alternate realities there are plenty of opportunities to describe so many different scenes, so vividly.</description></item></channel></rss>